daytranslations.com 2011-11-10

# Security & Privacy Policy

                        Security & Privacy Policy
Day Translations, Inc. Privacy Policy for Customers and Clients
At Day Translations, Inc. we pledge to maintain the utmost respect and confidentiality for
all of our client’s documents. Accordingly, Day Translations and all affiliates will use your
personal information only for the following purposes:
Our purpose in collecting personal information.
We collect your personal information only for the purpose of invoicing you on your
translation and sending you the final document. We do not store any of your personal
information or redistribute it to any outside parties. We only use personal information to:
     Contact you;
     Deliver the services you request;
     Develop and communicate special offers;
     Provide customer service;
What information we collect and how we collect it.
The information we collect may include:
     Contact information, phone numbers, service preferences, billing information, and
        other information you provide when you do business with us.
     Your location and industry.
How we use personal information.
     We do not sell or rent personal information to others.
     We do not use cookies on your website.
     We do not disclose personal information to non-Affiliates except in the instance
        that you request us to do so.

We take reasonable steps to protect your personal information.
We maintain a database of only your contact information and your original documents
and translated documents solely for the purpose of saving your files in case your need to
refer back to them and for our accounting purposes.
Modifications to our privacy policies.
We reserve the right to change our privacy policies at any time, except as may be
prohibited by law. We will post revisions online. Use of our services after posted changes
means that you consent to the privacy policies as changed.
Contact us for more information about our privacy policies.
If you have questions about our privacy policies, contact us at
Contact@daytranslations.com
Day Translations, Inc.,
415 Madison Avenue
New York City, NY 10017
(212) 537-6123

Revised Effective January 27, 2009
